Fire go higher
Wherever we are
BABYMONSTER girls got that woo woo ah
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
I’m like hot sauce
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
I don’t think you’re ready
Feeling deadly tonight
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N about to blow your mind
We about to leave you breathless
Call the doctors, paramedics
Cause the stage on fire
I’m not talking pyrotechnics
Got that chilli pepper, jalapeno
Too addictive red hot cheetos
Way we move hit like wasabi
BABYMONSTER bring the party
Step to the beat
Came ready to eat
You know we bring the flavor
Turn up the heat
They calling us beasts
Call it monster behaviour
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
I’m like hot sauce
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
I’m that little bit of everything,
whole lot of energy
Hundred miles an hour
you won’t never get ahead of me
Think you need a lemonade
Think you need a remedy
Ask me how I do it
It’s a secret recipe
Bet you never ever felt a fire like this
Carolina reaper kinda vibe like this
Sprinkle of pepper I’m stirring the pot
Get what I get cause I got what I got
We’ll do this all night baby,
we don’t get tired
The kinda energy that never expire
Red yellow green
Know you know what I mean yeah
’Bout to set it on fire
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
I’m like hot sauce
Hot sauce
Everybody want some
but can’t handle what I brought ’em
Fire go higher
Wherever we are
BABYMONSTER girls got that woo woo ah
Fire go higher
Wherever we are
BABYMONSTER girls got that woo woo
Hot sauce
Too hot hot
Yeah BABYMONSTER got that
Hot sauce
Too hot hot
Yeah BABYMONSTER got that